<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Work in Progress | Ruppy]]></title>
  <link href="http://ruppy.com.br/blog/categories/work-in-progress/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ruppy.com.br/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-24T17:56:45-03:00</updated>
  <id>http://ruppy.com.br/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ruppy Studio]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[hi@ruppy.com.br]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our First Game: Toledo Going Nuts]]></title>
    <link href="http://ruppy.com.br/blog/2014/03/24/our-first-game-toledo-going-nuts/"/>
    <updated>2014-03-24T15:05:24-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://ruppy.com.br/blog/2014/03/24/our-first-game-toledo-going-nuts</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="#en" class="english-button">You can read in English</a>
/
<a href="#pt" class="portuguese-button">Você pode preferir ler em Português</a></p>

<div class="english">
  <p>Hi everyone!</p>

  <p>As promised, today I’ll talk about the game we are making.
<strong>Toledo Going Nuts.</strong></p>

  <h3 id="history">History</h3>

  <p>You are Toledo, a peaceful rabbit that lives in a farm and love your cows.
Suddenly comes an alien, steal one of your cows and go away before you can do
anything.</p>

  <h3 id="villains">Villains</h3>

  <p>Toledo will face two types of villains: Aliens and Zombies. The Aliens will try
to abduct your cows all the time, but when they realize that without help they
will not succeed, it’s time to call out the Zombies. So don’t mind if, in the
middle of combat, one Taxi-Ship shows up bringing a Zombie. Just shoot to kill!</p>

  <p><img src="/assets/posts/sketch-ship-taxi-zombie.jpg" alt="Sketchs: Ship, Taxi and Zombies" /></p>

  <h3 id="platforms">Platforms</h3>

  <p>We are developing it for iPhones, iPod Touchs and iPads. And as soon as we
earn some money, we will port to Androids too. Using
<a href="https://unity3d.com">Unity</a> as our game engine will make it a lot easier.</p>

  <h3 id="website">Website</h3>

  <p>Along with the blog, we are releasing our website
<a href="http://ruppy.com.br/">ruppy.com.br</a> too! There are more information about the
game there and a kickass concept-art image. Be sure to check it out!</p>

  <p>Well, thanks for reading, stay tuned for more sketchs and game info. And if you
have any comments… comment!</p>

</div>

<div class="portuguese">
  <p>Fala galera,</p>

  <p>Como prometido, hoje vou falar um pouco sobre o jogo que estamos fazendo.
Ele chama <strong>Toledo Going Nuts</strong>, em bom português, Toledo ficando louco.</p>

  <h3 id="histria">História</h3>

  <p>No jogo, você é o Toledo, um coelho bem calmo que ama suas vacas. De repente,
um Alien aparece, rouba uma vaca e some antes que você possa fazer qualquer
coisa.</p>

  <h3 id="viles">Vilões</h3>

  <p>Toledo enfrentará dois tipos de vilões: Aliens e Zumbis. Os Aliens vão tentar
abduzir suas vacas o tempo todo, mas quando eles percebem que não vão conseguir
roubar todas sozinhos, eles pedem ajuda aos Zumbis. Então não repare se no meio
do tiroteiro, aparecer uma nave em formato de táxi trazendo um Zumbi.
Isso vai ser normal!</p>

  <p><img src="/assets/posts/sketch-ship-taxi-zombie.jpg" alt="Sketchs: Ship, Taxi and Zombies" /></p>

  <h3 id="plataformas">Plataformas</h3>

  <p>Toledo Going Nuts, está sendo feito para iPhone, iPod e iPad. Assim que
recebermos uma grana inicial, portaremos ele para Android também, o que não deve
ser muito complexto graças ao <a href="https://unity3d.com">Unity</a>, nossa engine de
desenvolvimento.</p>

  <h3 id="site">Site</h3>

  <p>Junto com o blog, estamos colocando nosso site
<a href="http://ruppy.com.br/pt-br">ruppy.com.br/pt-br</a> no ar também! Tem mais
informação sobre o jogo e um concept-art animal logo de cara. Dá uma olhada lá!</p>

  <p>Bom, por hoje é só! Obrigado por ler, fique ligado pra mais sketchs e
informações e qualquer comentário… comente!</p>

</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
